A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Pupil Placement Board, 1957-1966
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Applications, 1959-1966., Extent: 224.35 cu. ft. (641 boxes). (Box 87-728)
  - Subseries I. Special, 1959-1966., 6.3 cu. ft. (18 boxes) (Box 87-105)
    - Gloucester County, 1962-1965. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Goochland County, 1965. (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Grayson County, 1962-1965. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Greene County, 1962-1965. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Halifax County, 1964-1965. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Hanover County, 1963-1966. (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Henrico County (A - C), 1963-1966. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Henrico County (D - O), 1963-1966. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Henrico County (P - Y), 1963-1966. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - King and Queen County, 1963-1965. (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - King George County, 1962-1964. (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - King William County, 1963-1965. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Lancaster County, 1965. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Lee County, 1964-1965. (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Loudoun County, 1962-1966. (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Louisa County, 1962. (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Lunenburg County, 1965. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Madison County, 1964-1965. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Matthews County, 1961/1965. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Mecklenburg County, 1965. (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Middlesex County, 1963-1964. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery County, 1961-1964. (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Nansemond County, 1965. (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - New Kent County, 1965. (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Northampton County, 1964-1965. (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Northumberland County, 1965. (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Nottoway County, 1965. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Orange County, 1965. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Page County, 1965. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1965. (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Powhatan County, 1963-1964. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Prince Edward County, 1964-1965. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Prince George County(A - G), 1963-1965. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Prince George County(H - P), 1963-1965. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Prince George County(R - Y), 1963-1965. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Prince William County, 1961-1964. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Princess Anne County, 1961-1962. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Pulaski County, 1962-1963. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Rappanhannock County, 1964/1966. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Richmond County, 1965-1966. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Roanoke County(A - L), 1961-1966. (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Roanoke County(M - Y), 1961-1966. (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Rockbridge County, 1965. (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Rockingham County, 1964. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Russell County, 1965. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Scott County, 1964. (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Shenandoah County, 1963-1964. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Smyth County, 1965. (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1963-1965. (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Stafford County(A - H), 1961-1965. (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Stafford County(J - W), 1961-1965. (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Surry County, 1963/1966. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Sussex County, 1963-1965. (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Tazewell County(A - H), 1965. (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Tazewell County (J - Y), 1965. (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Westmoreland County, 1965-1966. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Wise County, 1964-1965. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Wythe County, 1964-1965. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Warren County, 1959-1966. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - York County, 1963-1965. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Alexandria (A-F), 1962-1965. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Alexandria (H-L), 1962-1965. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Alexandria (M-S), 1962-1965. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Alexandria (T-Z), 1962-1965. (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Bristol, 1964. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake, 1963-1965. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Covington, 1964. (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Danville, 1963-1965. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Fredericksburg, 1962-1965. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Galax, 1961-1966. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Hampton, 1963-1965. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Harrisonburg, 1964-1965. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Hopewell, 1960-1965. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Lynchburg, 1961-1963. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Martinsville, 1963/1964/1966. (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk (A-J), 1961-1965. (Box 98, Folder 1-5)
    - Norfolk (K-Z), 1961-1965. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Norton, 1963/1965. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Petersburg (A-G), 1962-1966. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Petersburg (H-O), 1962-1966. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Petersburg (P-Y), 1962-1966. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Portsmouth (A-L), 1962-1966. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Portsmouth (M-Z), 1962-1966. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Radford, 1963-1965. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Richmond (Administrative), 1965. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Richmond (A), 1961-1965. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Richmond (B-Bot.), 1961-1965. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Richmond (Bow. - By.), 1961-1965. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Richmond (C-H), 1961-1965. (Box 102, Folder 1-6)
    - Richmond (I-P), 1961-1965. (Box 103, Folder 1-4)
    - Richmond (Q-Z), 1961-1965. (Box 104, Folder 1-6)
    - Roanoke, 1961-1962. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Staunton, 1964-1965. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Suffolk, 1964-1965. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Beach, 1963-1964. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Waynesboro, 1960. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Williamsburg - James City, 1964. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Winchester, 1960-1966. (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Subseries II. Routine, 1957-1966., 217.7 cu. ft. (413 boxes) (Box 106-728)
    This subseries contains the applications the Pupil Placement Board considered routine, likely they are applications of students who sought placement in a school the board deemed appropriate. This does not mean that these applications contain no added notations; related records are included with the applications in this subseries and are filed with the applications they accompany. Examples of such records include correspondence explaining the lack of a birth certificate, letters of introduction, and student test score sheets. The test scores are restricted and sealed but remain in the collection. Applications for students in the City of Petersburg for school years 1960-1961 and 1961-1962 and the Counties of Brunswick and Chesterfield include tentative placement slips addressed to school principals. The slips serve to notify a school principal of a student's preliminary placement in their school until a birth certificate could be obtained or a complete application could be submitted and approved by the Pupil Placement Board. Applications for students coming from outside Virginia or requesting enrollment for the first time were originally submitted with birth certificates. Though the birth certificates are no longer in the collection, some applications feature certificate numbers written in the margin. Many of the Norfolk City applications from 1962-1964 include an attached form which contains the birth certificate information of the student, as well as, both parents full name and place of birth. A parent/guardian had to sign the form in addition to the school's principal to verify the information given as accurate.
    Fewer applications still were signed along with the phrase "Under Protest" accompanying the parent/guardians signature, but since these were filed as routine these parents likely objected to the existence of the board, not the placement of their child. There are also multiple applications for some students, usually the only difference is the school listed on the form, others are identical, but often there are discrepancies from application to application, such as, a student's name having two spellings (ex. Laurie, Lori or Stephen, Steven, Y and I are also used interchangeably Lynda, Linda, or IE for Y Sally, Sallie, last names also contain these mistakes but are not as easily caught since the forms are alphabetized), a birth date can also differ by month or year. This subseries contains applications dating from the 1960-1961 school year to the 1965-1966 school year. For unknown reasons there are some counties missing, as well as the bulk of applications for the 1960-1961 school year. It may be that some of the applications submitted for students seeking enrollment during the 1960-1961 school year were deferred until the 1961-1962 school year.
    A minimal number of applications have been restricted, a redacted copy of the application has been filed along with an envelope containing the sealed orginial. Applications have been sealed as personal information under code of Virginia 18.2-186.3, education records under Code of Virginia 2.2-3705.4(2) or 2.2-3705.1 (4) and Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), as well as social services records under Code of Virginia 2.2-3705.5 and 63.2(102-104).
    This subseries is arranged first by the school year for which enrollment is requested, thereunder alphabetically by city or county, and thereunder alphabetically by the pupil's last name, then first name, and for students with multiple application arrangement is chronologically.
    - Accomack County - Albemarle County (A - Clark), 1960-1962 (Box 106)
    - Albemarle County (Clarke - Z), 1960-1962 (Box 107)
    - Alleghany County - Amelia County, 1960-1962 (Box 108)
    - Appomattox County - Augusta County (A - H), 1960-1962 (Box 109)
    - Augusta County (I-Z) - Bath, 1960-1962 (Box 110)
    - Bedford County, 1960-1962 (Box 111)
    - Bland County- Botetourt County - Brunswick County(A-J), 1960-1962 (Box 112)
    - Brunswick County (K-Y) - BUckingham County - Campbell County (A-C), 1960-1962 (Box 113)
    - Campbell County (D-Y) - Caroline County, 1960-1962 (Box 114)
    - Carroll County - Charles City County - Charlotte County - Chesterfield (A-Bayton), 1960-1962 (Box 115)
    - Chesterfield County (Beaber - F), 1960-1962 (Box 116)
    - Chesterfield (G - Mize), 1960-1962 (Box 117)
    - Chesterfield County (Modjeski - Wade), 1960-1962 (Box 118)
    - Chesterfield County (Wadkins - Z) - Clarke County - Culpeper (A - Robinson), 1960-1962 (Box 119)
    - Culpeper (Rock-Y) - Cumberland County - Dickenson County, 1960-1962 (Box 120)
    - Dinwiddie County - Essex County, 1960-1962 (Box 121)
    - Fauquier County - Floyd County - Fluvanna County, 1960-1962 (Box 122)
    - Franklin County - Frederick County, 1960-1962 (Box 123)
    - Giles County 1960-1962 (Box 124)
    - Gloucester County - Goochland County - Grayson County - Greene County, 1960-1962 (Box 125)
    - Greensville County - Halifax County (A - Cole), 1960-1962 (Box 126)
    - Halifax County (Coleman - Peck), 1960-1962 (Box 127)
    - Halifax County (Penick - Z) - Hanover County(A - K), 1960-1962 (Box 128)
    - Hanover County (L-Z) - Henrico County (A - Britton), 1960-1962 (Box 129)
    - Henrico County (Broach - Day), 1960-1962 (Box 130)
    - Henrico County (DeAngelis - Hall), 1960-1962 (Box 131)
    - Henrico County (Haller - Lifsey), 1960-1962 (Box 132)
    - Henrico County (Light - Nabit), 1960-1962 (Box 133)
    - Henrico County (Nace - Saufley), 1960-1962 (Box 134)
    - Henrico County (Saunders - Wallo), 1960-1962 (Box 135)
    - Henrico County (Walls - Z) - Henry (A - G), 1960-1962 (Box 136)
    - Henry (H - Z), 1960-1962 (Box 137)
    - Highland County - Isle of Wight County - King and Queen County - King William County - Lancaster County - Lee County (A - C), 1960-1962 (Box 138)
    - Lee County (D - Y) - Loudoun County (A - F), 1960-1962 (Box 139)
    - Loudoun County (G - Z) - Louisa County 1960-1962 (Box 140)
    - Lunenburg County - Madison County - Mathews County - Mecklenburg (A - Clark), 1960-1962 (Box 141)
    - Mecklenburg County (Clary - Y), 1960-1962 (Box 142)
    - Middlesex County - Montgomery County (A - Hays), 1960-1962 (Box 143)
    - Montgomery County (Heavener - Z), 1960-1962 (Box 144)
    - Nansemond County - Nelson County (A - H), 1960-1962 (Box 145)
    - Nelson County (I - Z) - New Kent County - Norfolk County (A - Fish), 1960-1962 (Box 146)
    - Norfolk County (Fishel - Poole) 1960-1962 (Box 147)
    - Norfolk County (Pope - Z) - Northampton County (A - E), 1960-1962 (Box 148)
    - Northampton County (F - Z) - Northumberland County - Nottoway County (A - E), 1960-1962 (Box 149)
    - Nottoway County (F - Y) - Orange County, 1960-1962 (Box 150)
    - Page County - Patrick County - Pittsylvania County - Powhatan County - Prince George County (A - B), 1960-1962 (Box 151)
    - Prince George County (C - Z) - Princess Anne (A - Bazinet), 1960-1962 (Box 152)
    - Princess Anne County (Beard - H), 1960-1962 (Box 153)
    - Princess Anne County (I - Smelser), 1960-1962 (Box 154)
    - Princess Anne County (Smith - Z) - Pulaski County (A - Gravley), 1960-1962 (Box 155)
    - Pulaski County (Gray - Z), 1960-1962 (Box 156)
    - Rappahannock County - Richmond County - Roanoke County (A - Davidson), 1960-1962 (Box 157)
    - Roanoke County (Davis - Mobley), 1960-1962 (Box 158)
    - Roanoke County (Moir - Z), 1960-1962 (Box 159)
    - Rockbridge County - Rockingham County (A - H), 1960-1962 (Box 160)
    - Rockingham County (J - Z) - Russell County 1960-1962 (Box 161)
    - Scott County - Shenandoah (A - P), 1960-1962 (Box 162)
    - Shenandoah County (R - Y) - Smyth County - Southampton County, 1960-1962 (Box 163)
    - Spotsylvania County - Stafford County - Surry County - Sussex County - Warren County (A - F), 1960-1962 (Box 164)
    - Warren County (G - Z) - Washington County (A - L), 1960-1962 (Box 165)
    - Washington County (M - Y) - Westmoreland County, 1960-1962 (Box 166)
    - Wise County - Wythe County (A - C), 1960-1962 (Box 167)
    - Wythe County (D - Y) - York County (A - I), 1960-1962 (Box 168)
    - York County (J - Z) - Alexandria (A - Bowers), 1960-1962 (Box 169)
    - Alexandria (Bowington - Gardner), 1960-1962 (Box 170)
    - Alexandria (Garner - Lerch), 1960-1962 (Box 171)
    - Alexandria (Leslie - Ragland), 1960-1962 (Box 172)
    - Alexandria (Ramey - West), 1960-1962 (Box 173)
    - Alexandria (Wharton - Z) - Bristol, 1960-1962 (Box 174)
    - Coloial Heights - Covington (A - R), 1960-1962 (Box 175)
    - Covington (S - Y) - Danville (A - Ferris), 1960-1962 (Box 176)
    - Danville (Finley - Payne), 1960-1962 (Box 177)
    - Danville (Pearman - Z) - Fredericksburg (A - G), 1960-1962 (Box 178)
    - Fredericksburg (H - Z) - Galax - Hampton (A - Brinson), 1960-1962 (Box 179)
    - Hampton (Bristow - Elvey), 1960-1962 (Box 180)
    - Hampton (Emerson - Hilton), 1960-1962 (Box 181)
    - Hampton (Hingson - McDuffie), 1960-1962 (Box 182)
    - Hampton (McElheney - Reese), 1960-1962 (Box 183)
    - Hampton (Reese - Taylor, S.), 1960-1962 (Box 184)
    - Hampton (Taylor, T. - Z) - Harrisonburg, 1960-1962 (Box 185)
    - Hopewell (A - Trivett), 1960-1962 (Box 186)
    - Hopewell (Tucker - Y) - Lynchburg (A - D), 1960-1962 (Box 187)
    - Lynchburg (E - L), 1960-1962 (Box 188)
    - Lynchburg (M - Taylor), 1960-1962 (Box 189)
    - Lynchburg (Teague - Z) - Martinsville, 1960-1962 (Box 190)
    - Norfolk City (A - Bertz), 1960-1962 (Box 191)
    - Norfolk City (Beslow - Buttram), 1960-1962 (Box 192)
    - Norfolk City (Butts - Cowan), 1960-1962 (Box 193)
    - Norfolk City (Coward - Dutton), 1960-1962 (Box 194)
    - Norfolk City (Doty - Frazier), 1960-1962 (Box 195)
    - Norfolk City (Frederick - Harrell), 1960-1962 (Box 196)
    - Norfolk City (Harrington - Jackson), 1960-1962 (Box 197)
    - Norfolk City (Jacobs - Lamb), 1960-1962 (Box 198)
    - Norfolk City (Lambert - Maturs), 1960-1962 (Box 199)
    - Norfolk City (Mauch - Munden), 1960-1962 (Box 200)
    - Norfolk City (Mundy - Pierce), 1960-1962 (Box 201)
    - Norfolk City (Piercy - Russo), 1960-1962 (Box 202)
    - Norfolk City (Rust - Spry), 1960-1962 (Box 203)
    - Norfolk City (Squire - Vera), 1960-1962 (Box 204)
    - Norfolk City (Verdon - Wilmer), 1960-1962 (Box 205)
    - Norfolk City (Wilmoth - Z) Petersburg (A - Beasley), 1960-1962 (Box 206)
    - Petersburg (Beck - Curry), 1960-1962 (Box 207)
    - Petersburg (Curtis - Harriston), 1960-1962 (Box 208)
    - Petersburg (Hailslip - Kestner), 1960-1962 (Box 209)
    - Petersburg (Kevan - Nordyke), 1960-1962 (Box 210)
    - Petersburg (Norman - Simpson), 1960-1962 (Box 211)
    - Petersburg (Singleton - West), 1960-1962 (Box 212)
    - Petersburg (Whaley - Z) - Portsmouth (A - Bunn), 1960-1962 (Box 213)
    - Portsmouth (Bunting - Foster), 1960-1962 (Box 214)
    - Porstmouth (Fowler - Kee), 1960-1962 (Box 215)
    - Portsmouth (Keel - Presinger), 1960-1962 (Box 216)
    - Portsmouth (Peters - Tilton), 1960-1962 (Box 217)
    - Portsmouth (Timberlake - Z) - Radford, 1960-1962 (Box 218)
    - Richmond City (A - Cary), 1960-1962 (Box 219)
    - Richmond City (Cash - Frisby), 1960-1962 (Box 220)
    - Richmond City (Frith - Hyman), 1960-1962 (Box 221)
    - Richmond City (I - Modlin), 1960-1962 (Box 222)
    - Richmond City (Mollen - Ryland), 1960-1962 (Box 223)
    - Richmond City (S - Waggie), 1960-1962 (Box 224)
    - Richmond City (Wagner - Z) - Roanoke City (A-B), 1960-1961; 1961-1962 (Box 225)
    - Roanoke City (C - Hebert), 1960-1962 (Box 226)
    - Roanoke City (Heck - Newcomb), 1960-1962 (Box 227)
    - Roanoke City (Newman - Venable), 1960-1962 (Box 228)
    - Roanoke City (Vernon - Z) - South Norfolk (A - V), 1960-1962 (Box 229)
    - South Norfolk (W - Z) - Staunton - Suffolk (A - H), 1960-1962 (Box 230)
    - Suffolk (J - Z) - Williamsburg - Winchester, 1960-1962 (Box 231)
    - Accomack County (A - Mears), 1962-1964 (Box 232)
    - Accomack County (Melbourne - Z) - Albemarle County (A - B) 1962-1964 (Box 233)
    - Albemarle County (C - O), 1962-1964 (Box 234)
    - Albemarle County (P - Z) - Alleghany County (A - R), 1962-1964 (Box 235)
    - Alleghany County (S - Y) - Amelia County - Amherst County (A - S), 1962-1964 (Box 236)
    - Amherst County (T - Y) - Appomattox County - Augusta County (A - Call), 1962-1964 (Box 237)
    - Augusta County (Callison - Hutchinson), 1962-1964 (Box 238)
    - Augusta County (I - Scott), 1962-1964 (Box 239)
    - Augusta County (Scragg - Z) - Bath County (A - Routier), 1962-1964 (Box 240)
    - Bath County (Rucker - W) - Bedford County (A - F), 1962-1964 (Box 241)
    - Bedford County (G - O), 1962-1964 (Box 242)
    - Bedford County (P - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 243)
    - Bland County - Botetourt County (A -M), 1962-1964 (Box 244)
    - Botetourt County (N - Z) - Brunswick County (A - G), 1962-1964 (Box 245)
    - Brunswick County (H - T), 1962-1964 (Box 246)
    - Brunswick County (V - Y) - Buckingham County, 1962-1964 (Box 247)
    - Campbell County (A - G), 1962-1964 (Box 248)
    - Campbell County (H - P), 1962-1964 (Box 249)
    - Campbell County (Q - Y) - Caroline County (A - S), 1962-1964 (Box 250)
    - Caroline County (T - Y) - Carroll County - Charlotte County (A - I), 1962-1964 (Box 251)
    - Charlotte County (J - Y) - Chesterfield (A - Apel), 1962-1964 (Box 252)
    - Chesterdield County (Apgar - Benton), 1962-1964 (Box 253)
    - Chesterfield County (Berger - Brown, A.), 1962-1964 (Box 254)
    - Chesterfield County (Brown, B. - Carson), 1962-1964 (Box 255)
    - Chesterfield County (Carter - Corvello), 1962-1964 (Box 256)
    - Chesterfield County (Cosby - Faison), 1962-1964 (Box 257)
    - Chesterfield County (Faith - Hall), 1962-1964 (Box 258)
    - Chesterfield (Hallas - Hubbard), 1962-1964 (Box 259)
    - Chesterfield County (Hubble - Lake), 1962-1964 (Box 260)
    - Chesterfield County (Lamb - Mattingly), 1962-1964 (Box 261)
    - Chesterfield County (Matyiko - Newman), 1962-1964 (Box 262)
    - Chesterfield County (Newsome - Powell), 1962-1964 (Box 263)
    - Chesterfield County (Power - Sealey), 1962-1964 (Box 264)
    - Chesterfield County (Sealock - Sweet), 1962-1964 (Box 265)
    - Chesterfield County (Swenson - Waring), 1962-1964 (Box 266)
    - Chesterfield County (Warlick - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 267)
    - Clarke County - Culpeper County (A - D), 1962-1964 (Box 268)
    - Culpeper County (E - S), 1962-1964 (Box 269)
    - Culpeper County (T - Z) - Cumberland County - Dickenson County (A - G), 1962-1964 (Box 270)
    - Dickenson County (H - Y) - Dinwiddie County (A - B), 1962-1964 (Box 271)
    - Dinwiddie County (C - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 272)
    - Essex County - Fauquier County (A - J), 1962-1964 (Box 273)
    - Fauquier County (K - Z) - Floyd County, 1962-1964 (Box 274)
    - Fluvanna County - Franklin County (A - C), 1962-1964 (Box 275)
    - Franklin County (D - Slone), 1962-1964 (Box 276)
    - Franklin County (Smith - Z) - Frederick (A - Feltner), 1962-1964 (Box 277)
    - Frederick County (Ferguson - Q), 1962-1964 (Box 278)
    - Frederick County (R - Z) - Giles County (A - E), 1962-1964 (Box 279)
    - Giles County (F - Stafford), 1962-1964 (Box 280)
    - Giles County (Stanley -Z) - Gloucester County, 1962-1964 (Box 281)
    - Goochland County - Grayson County, 1962-1964 (Box 282)
    - Greene County - Greensville County (A - L), 1962-1964 (Box 283)
    - Greensville County (M - Z) - Halifax County (A - Boyles), 1962-1964 (Box 284)
    - Halifax County (Bradley - Elder), 1962-1964 (Box 285)
    - Halifax County (Ella - Lunsford), 1962-1964 (Box 286)
    - Halifax County (M - Stephen), 1962-1964 (Box 287)
    - Halifax County (Stephens - Z) - Hanover County (A - Brown), 1962-1964 (Box 288)
    - Hanover County (Bruce - S), 1962-1964 (Box 289)
    - Hanover County (T - Y) - Henrico County (A - Barre), 1962-1964 (Box 290)
    - Henrico County (Barrell - Brower), 1962-1964 (Box 291)
    - Henrico County (Bundy - Clark), 1962-1964 (Box 292)
    - Henrico County (Clarke - Degan), 1962-1964 (Box 293)
    - Henrico County (DeGon - Ferrante), 1962-1964 (Box 294)
    - Henrico County (Ferrell - Green), 1962-1964 (Box 295)
    - Henrico County (Greenburg - Herndon), 1962-1964 (Box 296)
    - Henrico County (Herring - Jones, G.), 1962-1964 (Box 297)
    - Henrico County (Jones, H. - Ligon), 1962-1964 (Box 298)
    - Henrico County (Liles - McGeorge), 1962-1964 (Box 299)
    - Henrico County (McGhee - Nicely), 1962-1964 (Box 300)
    - Henrico County (Nichol - Posky), 1962-1964 (Box 301)
    - Henrico County (Postans - Rust), 1962-1964 (Box 302)
    - Henrico County (Rustin - Smith, L.), 1962-1964 (Box 303)
    - Henrico County (Smith, M. - Thomasson), 1962-1964 (Box 304)
    - Henrico County (Thompkins - Webb), 1962-1964 (Box 305)
    - Henrico County (Webber - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 306)
    - Henry County (A - Goins), 1962-1964 (Box 307)
    - Henry County (Gonzolez - Moxley), 1962-1964 (Box 308)
    - Henry County (Moyer - Willey), 1962-1964 (Box 309)
    - Henry County (Williams - Z) - Highland County - Isle of Wight County - King George County, 1962-1964 (Box 310)
    - King and Queen County - King William County (A - S), 1962-1964 (Box 311)
    - King William County (T - W) - Lancaster County - Lee County (A - D), 1962-1964 (Box 312)
    - Lee County (E - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 313)
    - Loudoun County (A - L), 1962-1964 (Box 314)
    - Loudoun County (M - Z) - Louisa County (A - G), 1962-1964 (Box 315)
    - Louisa County (H - Y) - Lunenburg County, 1962-1964 (Box 316)
    - Madison County (A - Y) - Mathews County (A - S), 1962-1964 (Box 317)
    - Mathews County (T-Y) - Mecklenburg County (A - Harmon), 1962-1964 (Box 318)
    - Mecklenburg County (Harper - Roberts), 1962-1964 (Box 319)
    - Mecklenburg County (Robertson - Z) - Middlesex County - Montgomery County (A - Barnes), 1962-1964 (Box 320)
    - Montgomery County (Barnett - Haley), 1962-1964 (Box 321)
    - Montgomery County (Hall - Nuchols), 1962-1964 (Box 322)
    - Montogmery County (Nunley - Whisnant), 1962-1964 (Box 323)
    - Montgomery County (Whitaker - Z) - Nansemond County (A - Hill), 1962-1964 (Box 324)
    - Nansemond County (Hillard - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 325)
    - Nelson County - New Kent County - Norfolk County (A - Baysden), 1962-1964 (Box 326)
    - Norfolk County (Beacham - Gordy), 1962-1964 (Box 327)
    - Norfolk County (Gore - Moss), 1962-1964 (Box 328)